what's going on everybody sparks comics
here your marvel and indie comic
collector
and today i'm going to be doing
something a little bit different i'm
going to be doing a product review
of comic clear boards so
please after do the intro stick around
we're gonna check these boards out
welcome back everybody like i said we're
going to be doing a review of
comic clear boards today these are the
current birds that i bought they also
sell them in the silver
and golden age size versions
so any size for any type of comic that
you're trying to
to protect the way they describe them on
the paper is a crystal clear backing
board
archival pet plastic twice as thick as
standard backing boards
and a protective film to ensure boards
are scratch free
and so because we have that protecting
film here they say you need to use some
tape
and use that to pull off the protected
film so we're going to try that out
all right seems pretty pretty
straightforward now i gotta find
where i put my tape to get another piece
there it is
so piece on one side and
a piece on the other
i feel like i should be doing this with
gloves on because that is
crystal clear there
so this is the board without the film on
it
um it is pretty solid on the corners
so for me that means uh if a comic was
dropped
it's gonna be protected it's not as
thick
as you would get from a a fullback
but it's pretty thick and pretty sturdy
so i've got some mylar here i'm going to
throw this
into a mylar
my light um
maybe
so bagged and boarded together
pretty good combination there i figured
we got a clear back we want to look at
something cool in one of these right
so i have a venom 25 here
that i think is going to look excellent
in one of these bags
so let's try this out
right so front and back
that's pretty cool um so
i could um easily display front or back
depending on which side
of this wrap around cover
um so that's pretty cool i probably want
to put some clear tape on the back
though
instead of using the painters tape that
i've been using lately
otherwise that would look a little weird
[Music]
but otherwise that's pretty cool now
um looking at you know if i were to drop
this does it you know seem like it would
protect
this is probably a bad example because
this is a little bit of a bigger
sized book but um
yeah there we go if it's sitting in here
right it does
cover the full length like it should
uh now flexibility wise i've got
um full back here with venom 25
i can't can't really um
bend it in half i can kind of bend it
this way
a little a little bit of give that way
but pretty solid um otherwise
but the downside is you don't see the
rest of the wraparound cover
um flexibility here
this is just this kind of board is
given some protection but not a lot
um these are usually my standard type of
bags that i'll use
bags and boards for everyday pickups
things you're not trying to necessarily
really protect
i'll use the full backs more so or
half backs even for the ones that i want
to protect a little bit better
um but this honestly this looks um
this looks pretty good i'm i really
wasn't sure what to think
so i just bought one pack of these uh
because
you never know with a new product like
this um
what the results gonna be but these uh
honestly i think
i think i like these um so that's
awesome uh definitely gonna use them
in a situation like this or if there's
um one of those other books that i want
to protect really well
and it's older and you want to you know
see sometimes you want to see those like
weird old
ads that are on the back of the comics
and so i think that would be another
time
i would consider using these boards not
going to use them
for everyday stuff because i don't think
that's
a good use for them uh i think
those types of comics don't need that
extra protection
or that special
view window of the back because a lot of
those newer ones just have these really
boring ads on the back that are the same
ad over and over and over again so i
wouldn't want to use it on those
uh but overall i i think i'd recommend
using these boards
um for kind of almost
a little bit for the novelty of this uh
this window on the back we don't have
another board like this so i think
that would be one reason to use it and
i i think they're pretty sturdy i
honestly
do like the sturdiness of these boards
so just to kind of wrap that
up i had no sponsorship
by them to to do this review for you
guys so this was me
buying the boards um they were about 25
for a pack of 25 of them i think maybe
30 dollars at most
[Music]
shipping in there too so 25 30
for a pack of 25 so again not going to
want to use these on your everyday
comics because they're a little bit more
expensive i don't know if they still
have the deal running but they had a
deal where you bought
four of the packs and you'd get
one of those four for free so buy three
get one free uh i
almost did that but i didn't want to
spend that
much and then end up not liking them so
i may go back and do that now so you get
100 of them for the price of 75 of them
that's pretty good deal
um if hey see this video and want to you
know
give me a discount code that would be
awesome and i could put that
in the description but uh i doubt that's
going to happen
um but yeah so i i kind of like these as
something new
i figured i should do some product
reviews maybe some
talking about how i store my comics
another one i'd be interested in trying
out are the comic barricades
but my short boxes get a little full so
i wouldn't
use them very much so what i need to do
is get
more short boxes before i would consider
using those
i do want to talk about the bcw um
solid plastic bins too i think those are
uh a useful thing in my collection i'm
keep looking over here because i see
one or two of them um but yeah so i
think i'm gonna do some more
product review kind of things in the
future so keep an eye out for that
um and always remember guys collect what
you love
i'll see you guys next time
[Music]
you